Welcome to Policybazaar's Satisfaction Demo Video.
To start the activation process,
log in to Policybazaar with your registered mobile number.
After logging in, you will
see an activation notification.
Click on the Time Patient button. After that,
complete the video activation process. It is
important to complete this process before making the video.
First step: Keep the RC of the car and the previous year
's policy with you.
You will have to record it in the video.
Second step: Find the location of the car's chassis number.
Most of the chassis number is written under the front bonnet,
but in some cars, it is
also written near the door. Keep in
mind that only the chassis number is printed on the car's body and
not the one
affixed on the window or floor of the car. Third
step: Make this video in an
open place in daylight, such that it is
clearly visible in the courtyard. Keep in mind that while making the video, the shadow
of any building should
not fall on the car, nor should you make this video
within 20 minutes of parking at a repair workshop, petrol pump, etc. And the last step:
Before recording, take care to clean the eaves and
windows of the car.  Make sure to clean it as
you complete each step. Keep ticking on the screen
when all your settings are complete.
Now we are
ready.
You can easily make a video by reading the instructions on the screen to record your satisfaction video.
While recording, you can
also listen to the audience reaction in your preferred language.
Before starting the recording,
open the front bullet of the car.
Roll up and close all the windows of your car. Once the answer is
ready, click on the start recording button.
First record the front wind chill
from inside. Move the camera from left to right
and top to bottom in such a way
that the entire wind chill is recorded.
If there is any scratch or dent on the manual,
move the camera closer and record. Do
not use the camera angle at all.
[Music]
After this, record the RC of the car from both the front and back
sides. Keep in
mind that both sides of the RC can be easily read in the video.
Record all the pages of the previous year's policy copy. Make
sure that the
policy can be clearly seen and read in the video.
Start your car's engine and
record the kilometer reading on the auto meter. The
meter should show the total kilometers of your car,
meaning the number of kilometers your car has driven.
Some cars also have a trip meter
reading, but you should not record that.
This can cause your video to be rejected.
Record this type of number.
Most cars have the number written below the front bullet
as you can see in this video,
but in some cars it is
also written near the driver-passenger door. Keep in
mind that you are recording the chassis number printed on the body of the car,
not the
sticker on the windshield or floor of the car. Now,
lift the friend don't and record the engine compartment.
Now, after recording the engine,
turn off the Bullet and record something else from outside.
[Music]
Also, keep in mind that you are recording the entire video.
Now, move three to four meters away from the car and
record your car from the front. You have to make
sure that in this video, your
car is completely visible in the video, including the number plate.
Now, on to the
last step of the instruction process.  This is
very important.
Listen to the guidelines carefully and make a video of the car by moving around it.
We call this 360-degree
recording. Make sure that the
entire car's speed is
visible in the video frame and the recording is done
without any breaks. When you
reach the rear of the car while recording, record the number plate
and other things at the back clearly
so that you can see them clearly in the video.
[Music]
If there are any scratches or dents on the car,
go closer to it and record. Do
not use the camera angle at all.
Then come back to the maximum and
continue recording at the rear. When the video is
complete, check your video carefully to ensure
that you have recorded all the
important points keeping in mind.
If you forgot to record any step
or were
not able to record it correctly, then please record this video again.
If you are satisfied with the video, then
press the submit button and with this your
video conversion is complete.
Thank you for watching the demo video.
[Music]